♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
He's heading
for that cupe!
Come on, Jake.
Oh, yeah.
What?! He's gone.
What? What happened?
Hey, hey!
Did you guys see that?
You know that was a ghost
wearing a dead guy?
That might be the nastiest
thing I've ever seen.
N-n-n-n-nasty, nasty Jazz.
Nast...
Hey, hey! Easy, buddy.
That's our friend Billy.
He got possessed
by the Lich!
Oh, sorry! Sorry.
I didn't mean nothin' by it.
I mean, I have a
lot of nasty friends.
My uncle was nasty.
I'm basically
honorary nasty.
Do you know
where he went?
We have to find our friend.
Who knows.
Uh... oh.
Actually, it depends on
the wish I granted him.
Wish?
Yeah, he wished for the
extinction of all life,
and I did it.
I guess it changed his
timeline or something.
What?! Oh, glob!!
Whoa, wait a minute.
How can that be if
I'm still here kickin'
it with my main man,
Finn?
Oh, that's because you're
safe in my time room
until you make your wish.
Oh-h-h-h.
I wish that life
wasn't anymore exti...
Whoa! Wait, Jake.
Don't mess this up.
Think about it.
If we wish everything
back to normal,
the Lich could just
jazz it up again.
Oh, yeah.
Jazz.
Hmm.
Hm-m-m-m.
I got it!
I wish...
The Lich...
never...
even ever existed.
Mom?
Mom, what's wrong?
Finn, I need you to
do something for me.
It's very important.
I need you to take
the mule into
town today and sell him
for as much as you can.
What?
Sell Bartram?
But I love Bartram.
What the heck, mom?!
Shh!
Finn, please.
Just do as I say.
- Got it?
- Dad?
I push you.
You fall down.
The Destiny Gang?
Finn, please.
Everything will be fine,
I promise.
Now, just do as I say.
I'm sorry, Bartram.
I guess dad must be in real
trouble to be doing this.
But I bet there's a lot of fine
folk lookin' to buy a good mule.
Why, I bet I could even
come visit sometimes.
Won't that be swell,
Bartram?
Dang it, Bartram.
Bar-bar?
What the...
Bar-bar, how'd you
get up there?
Jake, look!
A golden crown!
Unbelievable!
We can sell it
and keep Bartram!
Bong bong!
Hold it right there!
Who are you?
I'm a thousand years old,
and this is my crown.
Okay, okay.
But, um...
maybe I could just...
borrow it for a little while?
No!
No! No!
This crown is magic.
Bad, terrible magic.
Too dangerous for mortal
fingies like yours!
One thousand years ago, my
beloved friend, Simon Petrikov,
gave his life to
save this foolish,
unworthy planet
from annihilation.
A frightful bomb
was poised to
bathe the land
in mutogenic horror.
But using his mastery
of ice and snow,
Simon froze the bomb in
mid-flight only inches
from the ground,
where it remains to
this very day,
today,
ever-ripe and
ready to blow.
But he alone
was not saved.
Trapped under the giant weight
of the enormous bomb,
poor Simon perished.
Little help?
And the horrible crown,
grieving its lost master,
loosed a spasm of magic
so wild and crazy,
the entire Earth was buried
in ice for 400 boring years.
Uh...
None of that is true,
'cause magic is fake.
Daddy says the false prophets
of old used cheap parlor tricks
to control the people,
and to get babes,
like 10 or 12
hot babes each.
No! Magic is real!
Lady, you been
down here too long.
- Why don't you just let...
- Step off, or I will use this!
Lady, quit it
with that thing!
I'm sorry.
You must die!
Aah?
Ooh.
Um...
Oh, man!
This thing...
dang it!
Go, Jake!
Aah!
Go back to the underworld, you beast!
Sorry!
I got to save my dad.
Destroy the world,
more like!
Dummy!
I give up.
The crown...
Go get it.
I know you're not
really talking to me.
I'm not crazy!
Get the crown!
Go get it!
Get the crown, Marceline!
I can't...
my knees!
Well, that's really
disappointing, I must say.
I'm just...
Well, whatever.
You're really letting
me down right now.
Okay. All right.
Cool crown!
Who wants a cool crown?!
I found it on a
dead magician dude!
I'll take it.
Awesome!
How much cash you got?
Oh, I'm poor.
Uh, but what about I trade
you for a personal concert
at your house?
I'll come over later and
sing you like four songs.
I mostly do covers,
but I have originals, too.
Do you own any spoons?
No.
Let me see that!
Hey!
Heh.
Wait. Destiny Gang.
I got to sell that
to pay you guys!
Trami, what you think?
Is it my style?
Big Destiny will know.
Yo, boss!
Snap!
Huh? What is this?
Are you telling me
what to wear, Trami?
No, boss!
You look good!
You think I should
re-invent my style
and put a stupid thing
on my head?!
No, man!
You tell us what to wear!
Otherwise, you would
dress like an idiot!
Bam! Crown shorts.
Amazing!
Yeah-ha-hah.
Clap harder, trash bag.
Okay, you guys.
Give me my money or
leave my parents alone.
Property of old dead person
go to Big Destiny.
One arm needs to
learn the rules,
unless you want your
butt handed to you.
I guess it wasn't
really mine.
It's mine!
I'm a demon.
Half demon.
Tromo, jack up crazy lady.
Trami, take mule back
to crib for din-din.
What?!
Bar-bar!
Tough luck, one-arm!
See you soon,
bad style junk town!
Bar-bar.
End of the road, bat lady.
Oww, my bones!
Aah!
My eye!
I will junk your face!
What the...
Destiny Gang,
get out of town!
We're sick of
being bullied around!
Yeah!
You make big mistake!
Especially you, one-arm.
My name is Finn Mertens!
And tell Big "D"
I'm coming for my stuff!
Oh, you come and try!
Are you okay, lady?
You must promise to...
promise to return the crown
to its hide-hole.
I promise.
You'll need this, Finn,
if you want to win.
Choose Bruce.
What is it?
It's a weapon for your arm.
With this,
you will defend from harm!
Hmm.
Feels natural,
like peeing outside.
Sort of.
Best not to take the lift,
my friend,
else the D-Gang
will see you coming in!
No.
I want them to see me.
I'm-a go up there and
show them my face!!
Aah?
Hello?
Bar-bar? I'm coming!
Bar-bar!
I want my stuff, you big dump.
You want Big D's crown, huh?
Yeah!
And Bar-bar!
Here you go, then.
Wha...?
That is your
final possession,
the last thing you
will ever own.
What do you... mean?
Look down there, stupid.
Town is on fire, see?
I made it on fire.
Fix up junk town.
Look at old man cry!
That's what happens
when you mess with Big D!
You get crush!
Your family get crush!
Boo-yah!
Suck my shirt!!
Jump!
Choose Bruce!
All my stuff is "goan!"
Now they're going after your...
Home!
Bar-bar, come on!
Hurry, Finn!
You can win!
Finn!
Return...
I will.
But we got to stop
the D-Gang first.
Come on, Jake!
Good boy!
Destiny!
No-o-o-o!!
Yeah!
How did I even
get here, son?!
Mom! Dad!
- Finn!
- No!
You said this
thing is magic?
Yes, powerful and dangerous.
But you lost your
mind in a cave.
Whatever.
You just got to
believe me, okay?
For serious,
you donk!
I am Big D!!
Whoo!!
I believe you.
You do?
Wait, no! Dingus!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪